(Amy:)Damn it, I got cocky.
(Howard:)Hey, Bernie.
I'm home.... Hello.
(Bernadette:)Hi, honey.
(Raj:)What's going on?
(Bernadette:)Maybe you should have a seat.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Howard:)I know my mom's not dead,
there'd be balloons.
(Raj:)First off, know that
we all love you and cherish you.
(Mike Rostenkowski:)-Well, I wouldn't--
-Daddy.
(Mike R:)You're great.
(Mike Massimino(on skype):)-Can I say something?
-Of course.
(Mike M:)Hey, Fruit Loops.
(Howard:)Massimino?
Why are you here?
(Mike M:)I heard you were thinking about going
back up to the space station,
(Mike M:)and as someone
who's been there with you....
Wall, you know how astronauts
need to have the 'right stuff"?
(Raj:)Sure.
(Mike M:)The stuff you have is wrong.
(Howard:)You don't think
I did a good job up there?
(Mike M:)You did a fine job.